<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote1>A small group of humans thought they saw something shiny in your colony and they want it. But we all know they're just looking for an excuse to smash something.</TwitchStoriesQuote1>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote2>Volunteers from a distant rival colony are coming to raid you. Fortunately, not too many of them, I would guess about tree fiddy.</TwitchStoriesQuote2>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote3>In the distance you hear: ... spear shall be shaken, shield shall be splintered, a sword-day, a red day, ere the sun rises!!!!!
DEEEEEEATH.... DEEEEEEATH.</TwitchStoriesQuote3>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote4>It's raining men! Hallelu- oh crap.</TwitchStoriesQuote4>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote5>Oh look, shooting stars!</TwitchStoriesQuote5>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote6>There are people marching towards your colony. There is no way to negotiate out of this. You just have to git gud and win the fight the old fashioned way.</TwitchStoriesQuote6>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote7>ALEXA! Play "Time to say goodbye"</TwitchStoriesQuote7>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote8>BUG PARTY! Inside the colony though.</TwitchStoriesQuote8>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote9>Looks like the last rejection broke {colonist}s heart.</TwitchStoriesQuote9>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote10>Guess who's back, back again, plague is back, on {colonist}</TwitchStoriesQuote10>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote11>AHA! {colonist} got "sick" and is not able to work, I see...</TwitchStoriesQuote11>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote12>Just a flesh wound! 'tis but a scratch! What do you mean by "Infection"?!</TwitchStoriesQuote12>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote13>Knock knock.
Who's there?
Amos...
Amos who?
Amosquito.</TwitchStoriesQuote13>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote14>Have you ever wondered what the insides of your stomach look like? Well lou wonderland no more, gut worms are here to give you the wisdom.</TwitchStoriesQuote14>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote15>{colonist} will not be able to make leg day anytime soon.</TwitchStoriesQuote15>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote16>The amount of events that have to go wrong, for half of your colony to get the plague, is astonishing. What have you done to these poor souls?</TwitchStoriesQuote16>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote17>A sneeze. A sneeze? A sneeze!! Get Down, someone is sneezing!!</TwitchStoriesQuote17>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote18>At least the colonists have learned, that "licking your wounds" is not a literal saying. But at a price.</TwitchStoriesQuote18>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote19>Mosquitos are like family. Annoying, but they carry your blood.</TwitchStoriesQuote19>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote20>Looks like the 5 second rule is not a thing here. As you hear: "Hey, I can still eat thi...Hoouuwwéééh", you see half of the colony's stomachs turn inside out. </TwitchStoriesQuote20>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote21>Mama always said, life is like a box of chocolates. You never know what you're gonna get. For example, muscle parasites.</TwitchStoriesQuote21>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote22>The Black Death has knocked on your door. You didn't answer, so the grim reaper himself kicked down the door and left everyone a little gift.</TwitchStoriesQuote22>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote23>This flu outbreak is obviously "not" caused by "someone" not washing their hands. *cough* {colonist} *cough*</TwitchStoriesQuote23>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote24>After a small stabbing contest has gotten out of hand, infections started to flourish. Why? Just why?</TwitchStoriesQuote24>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote25>You know the saying: "The sinking of the titanic was a miracle to the lobsters". Well, congratulations. You just saved a starving swarm of malaria mosquitos.</TwitchStoriesQuote25>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote26>There are many wonders of the human body. Starting to recognize a person by the sound of them vomitting is however none of them.</TwitchStoriesQuote26>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote27>You don't need to work out if you don't have any muscles.</TwitchStoriesQuote27>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote28>I guess they didn't see that coming.</TwitchStoriesQuote28>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote29>The weather is clearing up, go outside and PRAISE THE SUN! \[T]/</TwitchStoriesQuote29>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote30>Is god literally taking a piss or is this a blessing from the plant gods?</TwitchStoriesQuote30>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote31>When thunderstorms thought they weren't getting paid enough, they went on a lightning strike</TwitchStoriesQuote31>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote32>One strike and you're out!</TwitchStoriesQuote32>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote33>I don't care if it is summer or not, it is christmas time now!</TwitchStoriesQuote33>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote34>Looks like we are getting 6-8 inches of hard snow. At least Ygritte is happy...</TwitchStoriesQuote34>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote35>ＷＥ　ＧＥＴ　ＩＴ   you vape.</TwitchStoriesQuote35>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote36>Some unnatural weather has just occurred. A rain cloud is hanging one meter over the ground. Your colonists can feel the rain being created on them. </TwitchStoriesQuote36>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote37>Someone in your colony has played a "prank" and charged up enough static electricity to trigger lightning strikes. I wonder who it was...</TwitchStoriesQuote37>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote38>Is the moon blocking the sun, or is this the death star looking for a parking spot?</TwitchStoriesQuote38>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote39>I did not want to think about this but... the visual green light you humans call "aurora", is actually just sun-snot.</TwitchStoriesQuote39>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote40>The RimWorld gods decided to give some feedback on your colony...</TwitchStoriesQuote40>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote41>Ambrosia, or as Darwin's memoar said: "Dude, this fruit tastes like what weed smells like. No wait are you writing this down. No stahp".</TwitchStoriesQuote41>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote42>Some form of alien just landed in the area. Closer inspection reveals it's a dead {material} alien. In fact it's just {material}... But I WANT TO BELIEVE.</TwitchStoriesQuote42>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote43>If someone throws a stone at you, throw a flower at them. But remember to throw the flower pot along with it.</TwitchStoriesQuote43>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote44>One of your plants caught the flu - looks like you didn't vaccinate them. Guess you have to pay the price for this now...</TwitchStoriesQuote44>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote45>Shower thought: If the sun would be alive, would solar flares be kisses or a sneeze? </TwitchStoriesQuote45>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote46>Volcanic winter is a reduction in global temperatures caused by volcanic ash and droplets of sulfuric acid and water obscuring the Sun. That's wikipedia's language for "DAMN nature, you scary". </TwitchStoriesQuote46>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote47>Not enough vespene gas.</TwitchStoriesQuote47>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote48>And we gonna let it burn, burn, burn...</TwitchStoriesQuote48>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote49>What do you call a dad that got frozen?
A pop-sicle.</TwitchStoriesQuote49>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote50>What does a tornado and a divorce have in common? Someone is losing the house.</TwitchStoriesQuote50>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote51>You have my sword, and my bow, aaaaaaand 10 tornados which are heading towards you.</TwitchStoriesQuote51>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote52>{#male}Wild MAN?! TRIGGERED!!1{/male}{#female}Wild WOMAN?!! DID YOU JUST ASSUME MY GENDER!!1{/female}</TwitchStoriesQuote52>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote53>The wandering wanderer wonders on the wonder of wonders. Oh how the wonder of wonders wonders. </TwitchStoriesQuote53>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote54>Chat decided {colonist} looks better as a {gender}.</TwitchStoriesQuote54>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote55>Against all expectations, {colonist} got better at {skill}.</TwitchStoriesQuote55>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote56>It is the day of the potato, time to party!!!</TwitchStoriesQuote56>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote57>Let's beat the devil out of it - Bob Ross</TwitchStoriesQuote57>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote58>One animal was targeted by a psychic weapon and was driven to madness. </TwitchStoriesQuote58>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote59>A herd of {animal} is on it's way to the abyss and will travel through the area.</TwitchStoriesQuote59>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote60>Did you know? A group of bears is called a sloth, but a group of sloths doesn't have a herd noun because they are too lazy group up.</TwitchStoriesQuote60>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote61>What sounds more real? A horse with a simple horn on its forehead or a long neck, fabulous fur and a giant axe on its forehead. You decide.</TwitchStoriesQuote61>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote62>You always wanted a pet? Or {amount}? Well, I guess today is your lucky day.</TwitchStoriesQuote62>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote63>Not sure if this animal knows what it has signed up for, but it has decided to join your colony.</TwitchStoriesQuote63>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote64>Who doesn't like yorkshire terriers? Just look at these adorable creatures! And a whole pack wants to sniff at your colonists butts, this must be paradise :)</TwitchStoriesQuote64>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote65>A number of local {animal} has gone insane and want to ensure the survival of their species. They believe you want to hunt and eat them.</TwitchStoriesQuote65>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote66>Don't worry, they just want to cuddle... Or do they?</TwitchStoriesQuote66>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote67>The RimWorld gods have touched your colony. {colonist} was blessed and will have a crumble of gods power. </TwitchStoriesQuote67>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote68>As the earth is trying to reject you, it sends some of the animals in the local area to kill you. Get ready.</TwitchStoriesQuote68>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote69>No no, I am definitely not insane, it is just the drone...</TwitchStoriesQuote69>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote70>Every colonist gets the feeling when you've got an unknown song in your head all day, and then finally figure out what song it is.</TwitchStoriesQuote70>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote71>I have not lost my mind. Half of it just wandered off and the other half went looking for it.</TwitchStoriesQuote71>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote72>Honestly, I don't even play an active role in my life anymore... Things just happen and I'm like "Oh, is this what we're doing now? Ok."</TwitchStoriesQuote72>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote73>Sometimes I question my sanity, but the unicorn and gummy bears told me I'm fine!</TwitchStoriesQuote73>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote74>Execute order 66.</TwitchStoriesQuote74>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote75>A chunk of a ship has crashed near the colony. It's amazing that those never seem to have any tech in it, just metal.</TwitchStoriesQuote75>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote76>Your {item} delivery is here! What? You haven't ordered this? Well, I won't take it with me again, it's your problem now!</TwitchStoriesQuote76>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote77>All hail the RimWorld gods. They bless us with their gifts and we shall return it with blood.</TwitchStoriesQuote77>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote78>This thing looks venom-enal, we should go and check it out.</TwitchStoriesQuote78>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote79>8-Ball, should we go and explore the ship part? Reply hazy, try again.</TwitchStoriesQuote79>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote80>Every colony needs a golden throne!</TwitchStoriesQuote80>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote81>But first, let me take a selfie. *flashy-thinged*</TwitchStoriesQuote81>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote82>I wonder how long it'll take until they try to flee from this colony...</TwitchStoriesQuote82>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote83>Another colony sent a caravan out to explore, however, they forgot about it and they are now exploring forevermore.</TwitchStoriesQuote83>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote84>Some visitors are here and ever since they arrived, there is a weird smell of fish around them. Where did they get the fish from?</TwitchStoriesQuote84>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote85>Today's special offer, buy one, pay two.</TwitchStoriesQuote85>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote86>"Veni, vidi, VISA", I came, I saw, I did a little shopping.</TwitchStoriesQuote86>
  <TwitchStoriesQuote89>Pleasure without regrets.</TwitchStoriesQuote89>
</LanguageData>